mobissimo.com 2007-12-22

# Mobissimo Travel | Privacy policy

Thank you for visiting this Internet web site located at www.mobissimo.com ("Site"). This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout Mobissimo governing Mobissimo's use of personally identifiable information provided to Mobissimo via this Site, as well as other information collected via this Site. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
  
You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. We collect personally identifiable information about you only if you voluntarily provide it to us and you have the option not to provide any personally identifiable information to us. You may voluntarily provide to us personally identifiable information when you register for the service and when you submit a request for travel services to the Site. We may use your personally identifiable information to respond to your requests for information about possible travel arrangements or about Mobissimo itself. 

**Cookies**  
  
We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you. Additionally, our search partners may use cookies during your visits to their External Web Sites (defined below) and their use of cookies may be subject to their own privacy policies. Mobissimo's search partners do not have access to Mobissimo's cookies.

We allow advertisers and other third parties to place cookies on this Site for the purpose of tracking some of the web searches, browsing and clicks made on this Site, customizing ads to you on this Site and other web sites you visit, and/or keeping track of your response to each ad. None of these third parties are able to use this information to identify you personally. One such company is AlmondNet. If you'd like to know more about AlmondNet's privacy practices, please click [here](http://www.almondnet.com/privacy.aspx?miid=7).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [ here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

**Aggregate Information**  
  
The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, and the domain names of our users' Internet Service Providers, and we may analyze these data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. Such aggregate information is not linked to any personally identifiable information that can identify any individual person. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**Disclosure**  
  
Any organization to which we provide your personally identifiable information will also required to keep your personally identifiable information confidential in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any other company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Mobissimo participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Mobissimo's assets. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**Links To Third Party Sites**  
  
This Site includes links to other World Wide Web sites or resources ("External Web Sites"). Because Mobissimo has no control over External Web Sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that Mobissimo is not responsible for the availability of such External Web Sites or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such External Web Sites or resources. You further acknowledge and agree that Mobissimo shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such External Web Site or resource. Finally, you acknowledge that such External Web Sites usually have their own terms and conditions, including privacy policies, over which Mobissimo has no control and which will govern your rights and obligations with respect to the use of those External Web Sites. 

**Children**  
  
In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), this Site is not intended for children under 18 years of age. Mobissimo does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. 

**Correction/Updating/Deleting Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
Mobissimo provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. If you wish to review, correct or delete any information you have provided to us, you may contact Mobissimo by [email](mailto:webmaster@mobissimo.com), by telephone at 650-577-2300 or at the following postal address:   
Mobissimo, Inc.   
Attention: Webmaster   
631 Howard St.   
Suite 520   
San Francisco, California 94105   

**Privacy Policy Updates**  
  
Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, Mobissimo may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Mobissimo will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site so users are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. Mobissimo encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated: April 12, 2006

This Privacy Policy is effective as of: April 12, 2006
